(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T00:21:51.735857",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
WAH!
Good Morning, Afternoon, and Evening!
It's me, Ina!
I hope everyone is excited for the concert!
I know I am!
I've been AmiAmi's ambassador for a full year now,
and it's been so much fun sharing all the great memories and the cool merch with you!
I've been using AmiAmi for a long time,
but I still get excited every time I spot something WAHnderful on AmiAmi
- it's like finding treasure!
Whenever you find cute merch of your oshi on AmiAmi, be sure to let us know, okay?
Let's give AmiAmi a big thank you for everything they've done this year!
Everyone say, Thank you AmiAmi!
Anyways, let's make more amazing memories tonight!
Make sure to cheer with everything you've got, okay?
WAH!
本能が狂い始める
My instincts start to go crazy,
追い詰められたハツカネズミ
Like a cornered mouse,
今、絶望の淵に立って
Now, standing in an abyss of despair,
踏切へと飛び出した
You jump into the railroad crossing
そう 君は友達
Yes, you're my friend,
僕の手を掴めよ
So take my hand
そう 君は独りさ
Yes, you're alone,
居場所なんか無いだろ
You've got nowhere to go, do you?
二人きりのこの塒
In this hideout of just the two of us,
愛し合えるさ…
We're able to love each other...
繰り返す
It repeats again;
フラッシュバック・蝉の声・
A flashback, the buzzing cicadas...
二度とは帰らぬ君
And you, who will never come back.
永遠に千切れてく
Are being torn apart for all eternity.
お揃いのキーホルダー
Our matching keychains
夏が消し去った
That the summer got rid of
白い肌の少女に
The girl with her pale white skin
哀しい程取り憑かれて仕舞いたい
I find myself wanting to be possessed by her so much it brings me to tears
本能が暴れ始める
My true nature starts to break loose
九月のスタート
At the start of September,
告げるチャイム
Marked by the ringing of chimes
次の標的に置かれた花瓶
A flower vase placed on the next target,
仕掛けたのは僕だった
And the one who started it... was me
そう 君が悪いんだよ
It's true, you're to blame--
僕だけを見ててよ
Just look at me and me only
そう 君の苦しみ
It's true, you want someone to help you,
助けが欲しいだろ
Don't you?
溺れてくその手に
I gently place a kiss
そっとキスをした…
On your drowning hands
薄笑いの獣達
Those faintly smiling beasts
その心晴れるまで
Until their hearts are refreshed,
爪を突き立てる
Dig their nails into you
不揃いのスカート
And now your skirt is uneven
夏の静寂を切り裂くような悲鳴が
A scream that seemed as though it cut off the silence of summer
こだまする教室の窓には青空
Echos through the classroom, in the window is the blue sky
愛のネタバレ
Love's spoiler
「別れ」っぽいな
Feels like a breakup
人生のネタバレ
Life's spoiler
「死ぬ」っぽいな
Feels like death
なによそれ意味深で
What's with that, so meaningful
かっこいいじゃん…
And pretty cool...
それっぽい単語集で
Dancing to a collection
踊ってんだ
of such-like words
失敬
Pardon me
とぅ とぅるる とぅ とぅるる 風
Tu-tururu tu-tururu style
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
Feels like it, feels like it
神っぽいな
God-ish, huh
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That's enough, that's enough, yeah
もういいぜ もういいぜ
That's enough, that's enough
逆に興奮してきたなあ
I'm actually getting kind of excited
おっけいね おっけいね 夢
Okay, okay, a dream
景気いいけれど 品性はthe end
Things are booming, but class is the end
うぇえい うぇえい
Yay, yay
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
God-ish, that's vulgar
神っぽいな それ "my god"
God-ish, that's 'my god'
アイウォンチュー ウォンチュー
I want you, want you
IQが下がっていく感じ
Feeling my IQ dropping
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
Evil-ish, after all
邪心っぽいな それ "my god"
Evil-ish, that's 'my god'
アイヘイトチュー ヘイトチュー
I hate you, hate you
害虫はどっちん
Which one's the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that makeup
アレっぽいな それ 比喩
That's something-ish, that's a metaphor
その名言 その意見 その批評
That quote, that opinion, that criticism
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, that gag, that sense
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
God-ish, that's vulgar
っぽいな っぽいな っぽい
Something-ish, something-ish, something
憧れちゃう！
I admire it!
愛のネタバレ
Love's spoiler
「別れ」っぽいな
Feels like a breakup
人生のネタバレ
Life's spoiler
「死ぬ」っぽいな
Feels like death
なによそれ意味深で
What's with that, so meaningful
かっこいいじゃん…
And pretty cool...
それっぽい単語集で
Dancing to a collection
踊ってんだ
of such-like words
失敬
Pardon me
とぅ とぅるる とぅ とぅるる 風
Tu-tururu tu-tururu style
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
Feels like it, feels like it
神っぽいな
God-ish, huh
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That's enough, that's enough, yeah
もういいぜ もういいぜ
That's enough, that's enough
逆に興奮してきたなあ
I'm actually getting kind of excited
おっけいね おっけいね 夢
Okay, okay, a dream
景気いいけれど 品性はthe end
Things are booming, but class is the end
うぇえい うぇえい
Yay, yay
"Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
God-ish, that's vulgar
神っぽいな それ "my god"
God-ish, that's 'my god'
アイウォンチュー ウォンチュー
I want you, want you
IQが下がっていく感じ
Feeling my IQ dropping
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
Evil-ish, after all
邪心っぽいな それ "my god"
Evil-ish, that's 'my god'
アイヘイトチュー ヘイトチュー
I hate you, hate you
害虫はどっちん
Which one's the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, those clothes, that makeup
アレっぽいな それ 比喩
That's something-ish, that's a metaphor
その名言 その意見 その批評
That quote, that opinion, that criticism
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, that gag, that sense
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
God-ish, that's vulgar
っぽいな っぽいな っぽい
Something-ish, something-ish, something
憧れちゃう！
I admire it!
Ooh
Just look around and see, it’s so incredible
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you’ll be dazzled
There’s magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let’s shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We’re on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you’re here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite, we’re gonna shine bright
Together, we’re all for one, all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in, ‘cause it’s all for one, all for one
We’re on our way to good times, good vibes
We’ll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we’re striving toward
We’re singing, all for one, all for one
Everything’s in motion, get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We’re joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let’s shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We’re here together, finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There’s a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we’re all for one, all for one
We’ll sing in harmony and we’ll be happy
Jump in, ‘cause it’s all for one, all for one
Keep up the hype, it’s good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way
We’re shining, all for one, all for one
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope
We’ll gather and we’ll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul
We’re here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I’m with you
I could swear it’s like a wish is coming true
So I’ll believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
When our voices and hearts unite, we’re gonna shine bright
Together, we’re all for one, all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in, ‘cause it’s all for one, all for one
We’re on our way to good times, good vibes
We’ll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we’re striving toward
We’re singing, all for one, all for one
Mori Calliope
MYTH
Mori Calliope · Takanashi Kiara · Ninomae Ina'nis
Hakos Baelz
PROMISE
IRyS · Ouro Kronii · Hakos Baelz
Shiori Novella
Nerissa Ravencroft
ADVENT
Shiori Novella · Koseki Bijou · Nerissa Ravencroft · Mococo Abyssgard · Fuwawa Abyssgard
Gigi Murin
JUSTICE
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame · Gigi Murin · Cecilia Immergreen · Raora Panthera
hololive English 3rd Concert ALL FOR ONE
Just look around and see, it's so incredible
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide
And suddenly, you're here by my side
When our voices and hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright
Together, we're all for one, all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one, all for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one, all for one
Everything's in motion, get up and start the celebration
Come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see
Feel the love and the energy
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom, my heart goes boom, boom, boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud, our time is right now
We're here together, finally
Every moment takes my breath away
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
Together, we're all for one, all for one
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one, all for one
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way
We're shining, all for one, all for one
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road
Feel the music in your passionate soul
We're here right now, so let the good times roll
Every time that I'm with you
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me
Together we can chase all our dreams
When our voices and hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright
Together, we're all for one, all for one
The thrill of happiness is all around us
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one, all for one
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward
We're singing, all for one, all for one
Time to open up your eyes, feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be, living life so fast and free
Got to keep your eyes on me, music is my story
Time to open up your eyes,
Feel the music start to rise,
Got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free, try to keep your eyes on me,
'Cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
Ready to play? Come at me
Carried away so easy, I can't get enough!
Free as a bird, no limit / Haven't you heard? I'm fearless
Get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Watch me be your diva,
I'm gonna raise your fever,
Shakin' up all the crowd, making some noise when I'm not allowed,
Livin' my life out loud,
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding,
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
Now pay attention, please
'Cause this is only the beginning -
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc,
How do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness.
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Midnight, draw me to the dark side,
Daylight, take me on a joyride,
My crime is my passion, I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is: This is our genesis.
Gonna start the rave, when I misbehave, take center stage
Let the fun commence, but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken; the rules can all be broken,
I'm runnin' on a rampage, the world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory,
They're gonna know me by name!
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands.
But they don't understand that I'm a star in the making...
Tell me how you like me now!
Come and watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me -
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control
Ready? You've got to free your mind
Leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is! It's our genesis
Time to open up your eyes,
Feel the music start to rise, got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be livin' life so fast and free, try to keep your eyes on me,
'Cause this is our beginning, it's our genesis!
Whispers banging down your window, rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion, I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is: This is our genesis.
You know what time it is? It's our genesis
Tell me what time it is! It's our genesis
Yeah! You know what time it is? It's our genesis
霧の夢に眠る綿津見
Magic pages open wide, spilling secrets from inside
器重ね蘩む檜
Now the story stirs again, a tale that never ends
割れて白く夢は紅
Distant waves, they call to me
染めてわらべうたは途絶え消えた
Echoing a memory
刻々と壊されて
Melancholic and forlorn
誰もしれない手紙
Nostalgia reborn
Abyssal hymn
時の虚眠る我が罪
Now it is time to find myself
孤独わらべうたの律
That frightened infant of the past
マジカルな呪いと身の毛のよだつ
Magical curses and hair-raising,
忌々しい迷信を
vile superstitions—
拭ってよ
wipe them away!
始まりへと
Toward the beginning,
終わりへと向かって 縦に描いていくのは
and toward the end, what we draw vertically
破片のように浮かび上がってくるのは
are things floating up like fragments,
刃のよう 飛び越えただけ
jumping right over them like blades.
赤かった
It was red,
そこにいたら教えてほしいの
if you're there, tell me please.
私が歩くこの道は
The path I walk on,
どんないろだろう
what color will it be?
ああ、この調べの
Ah, this melody's
戦慄を
shudder...
空に手を
Hands reaching to the sky
伸ばし始める
begin to stretch out.
知りたかった
I wanted to know,
多くの血の道が
the path of much blood.
愛を渇望して
Thirsting for love,
泣き叫んでる
crying out in tears.
始まりへと
Toward the beginning,
終わりへと向かって 縦に描いていくのは
and toward the end, what we draw vertically
救われた
was saved,
君の声
your voice.
愛しい
My beloved
異物よ そこにいたら教えて
foreign object, if you're there, tell me.
君の手をいつかまた
Your hand, someday once more
握れるの この
can I grasp it?
It's finally time!
We're here! We're here!
Well, shall we?
We shall. You go first.
I go first?
You go first.
Okay.
You know the drill, guys!
Ina'nis here! Ina'nis here! Wah! Wah!
Good morning, afternoon, evening! This is Ninomae Ina'nis of Ho—
You got this, you got this!
I just—I saw—I'm tired.
And we have—
One, two, three, four! I am Chaos, the end of everything!
Life is a gamble, so trust me with this!
Guys! How was that for an opener?
Did you guys enjoy it?
I can't hear you!
And of course, everyone watching from home, hello! We see you guys!
We have arrived at Hololive English 3rd Concert, All For One!
Bae, how do you feel?
I feel fantastic!
Fantastic!
Miraculously preserved.
You know, I can't believe it's already the third live. First, we conducted the world.
Second, we broke the dimension. And third...
We are... All For One!
Did you guys like? I guess this is the first time we're all together performing all for one.
Did you guys like it? I guess this is the first time we're all together performing All For One.
Yeah!
Oh man, I almost cried.
I know.
You know, and I were like, we were like, oh my god, so emotional.
Um, but I hope you guys enjoyed the open that we had, Advent...
And had... we had... Ini's solo.
And had... we had... Ina's solo.
It was so good! Did you guys like it?
Oh my goodness! All right, you know, since it is the very bae, it's the first...
Oh my goodness! All right, you know, since it is the very, it's the first...
This is the first MC of the first day! We're just getting started.
We need to test those penlights! Yeah, test the penlights! All right!
How about we split them in the middle here and go...
Purple... no not purple! Violet here!
It keeps on telling, okay? And violet here, and red...
And over here, I want to see red! Red!
Oh my goodness! I always get so emotional, emotional seeing, seeing you penlights.
Oh my goodness! I always get so emotional, emotional seeing, seeing your penlights.
Well yeah, you know, not only that, you know, we're just getting started, the whole show today and tomorrow.
So make sure to share it with everyone, share your excitement with hashtag #holoAllForOne!
Do I get to do the next part? Finally, you're doing this time.
Do I get to do the next part? Finally, you're doing it this time.
Although it is kind of a sad news.
Wait, wait, no, it's just I've never done it before. I'm really excited, but...
She's excited, but it's not, it's kind of sad because it is now time to announce that...
She's excited, but it's kind of sad because it is now time to announce that...
I have terrible news! Oh, what is it?
Unfortunately, if you are watching from home, this is the end of the free segment!
How could this be? Absolute tragedy!
This is a tragedy, but do not worry, if you are at home and you just saw this bang over opening, you want to continue watching the rest of the concert, check the link in the description, get your tickets, and continue watching the concert.
This is a tragedy, but do not worry, if you are at home and you just saw this banger of an opening, you want to continue watching the rest of the concert, check the link in the description, get your tickets, and continue watching the concert.
Not you guys! You guys, you guys are just stuck here until the end, all right?
You'd better be ready with your unlimited energy!
Yeah, I think we should, you know, get, test a little bit. Are you guys ready?
Ready! All right, you know the drill.
Do they know the drill? Do I know the drill? You know the drill, believe it.
All right, on the count of... Well, count down from... Count down from three!
Three, two, one...
All For One!
Elizabeth Rose Bloodflame
Cecilia Immergreen
Gigi Murin
Raora Panthera
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.
just look around and see-it 's so incredible !
Just look around and see, it's so incredible!
so many smiles in a sea of light
take one step with me and you 'll be dazzled ,
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled,
there 's magic in the air tonight
There's magic in the air tonight
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
the world is brighter because you believe in me
let 's shout it loud loud loud
Let's shout it loud loud loud,
our time is right now
we 're on the edge of destiny
We're on the edge of destiny
for a moment , i can dream with you
For a moment, I can dream with you
every miracle we hoped for might come true
we come together , reaching out from far and wide ,
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
and suddenly , you 're here by my side !
And suddenly, you're here by my side!
when our voices and hearts unite , we 're gonna shine bright !
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together , we 're all for one .
Together, we're all for one.
(let 's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us !
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in , \u2018 cause it 's all for one
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let 's sing ! all for one ! ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!!)
we 're on our way to good times , good vibes
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
we 'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey !
Hey!
all that we waited for , the dream we 're striving toward ,
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we 're singing , all for one !
We're singing, all for one!
all for one !
All for one!
everything 's in motion ,
Everything's in motion,
get up and start the celebration ,
Get up and start the celebration,
come see the wonders here beyond imagination
we 're joining hands for the world to see ( uh - huh )
We're joining hands for the world to see (Uh-huh)
feel the love and the energy !
Feel the love and the energy!
the hours zoom zoom zoom
my heart goes boom boom boom
a dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
let 's shout it loud loud loud
Let's shout it loud loud loud,
our time is right now
we 're here together , finally !
We're here together, finally!
every moment takes my breath away ;
Every moment takes my breath away;
there 's a feeling here that words cannot convey ,
There's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
we hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song ,
We hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
and suddenly , our hearts beat as one !
And suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
every voice ringing loud and clear , so glad to be here
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
together , we 're all for one .
Together, we're all for one.
(let 's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
we 'll sing in harmony and we 'll be happy
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
jump in , \u2018 cause it 's all for one
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let 's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
keep up the hype , it 's good times good vibes
Keep up the hype, it's good times good vibes
remember this night the rest of our lives
hey !
Hey!
raise up your hands and sway , your light will lead our way ,
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
we 're shining , all for one !
We're shining, all for one!
all for one !
All for one!
so bring your memories , your joy and your hope ,
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
we 'll gather and we 'll sing upon this endless road , oh , oh
We'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
feel the music in your passionate soul ,
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
we 're here right now , so let the good times roll , oh , oh
We're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
every time that i 'm with you ,
Every time that I'm with you,
i could swear it 's like a wish is coming true
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
so i 'll believe in you if you believe in me ,
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
together we can chase all our dreams !
Together we can chase all our dreams!
( 1 , 2, 3 , 4 , 5 ! )
(1, 2, 3, 4, 5!)
when our voices and hearts unite , we 're gonna shine bright !
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright!
together , we 're all for one .
Together, we're all for one.
(let 's sing ! all for one ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!)
the thrill of happiness is all around us !
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
jump in , \u2018 cause it 's all for one
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
(let 's sing ! all for one ! ! )
(Let's sing! All for one!!)
we 're on our way to good times , good vibes
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
we 'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
hey !
Hey!
all that we waited for , the dream we 're striving toward ,
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we 're singing , all for one !
We're singing, all for one!
all for one !
All for one!